sathacks.net 2014-06-25

# SaT Prepar-SaT-Dz TeaM

## SUPPORT

Support!

Absence des administrateurs,laissez un message SVP.

  * 
  * SaT-Dz Tech
  * Coupe du Monde de la FIFA 2014™
  * Sport
  * Free Server
  * Contactez nous

Ou somme-nous?!

\- 

**Visiting my brother .. We use advertising companies as a third party to display ads, and when you visit our website, it is entitled to these companies that use information about your visits to this site (except for name, address or e-mail address or telephone number) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest by cookie DART. Can prevent the use of the [DART](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) cookie by clicking [here](http://optout.doubleclick.net/cgi-bin/optoutgoogle.pl/). If you want to know the choices available to you to prevent such information from being used by these companies and more information about the privacy policy of this site, please read this page carefully.We Sathacks, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. Policy in this [document outlines the types](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) of personal information we collect and how it is used by us and by our advertisers.We TRAIDNT use Google ads, as external financial resource, so use Google cookies to serve ads on our site.  
And so you will be able to Google, using the cookie DART, display ads based on the interests of users based on their visit to our TRAIDNT.  
And, of course, can to Zorana customers disable the use of the DART cookie [visit the privacy policy of the Google ad and content network.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)Log Files:Like many other Web sites, and hence the [Sathacks](http://www.sathacks.net/) use of log files. This includes internet protocol (addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date / time, and number of clicks to analyze trends). Here and in the process it is not intended that collect all this information in order to eavesdropping on things visitors personal, but they are things analytical purposes to improve the quality of ads by Google, and added to it that all this information stored by us completely confidential, and remain within the scope of development and our website improvement only.Cookies and network settings: The company Google does use cookies to store information about interests of visitors, along with a special register the user record specific information on which pages the user access or visit, and this step we know how concerns visitors and any topics most preferred by them so we can do our part develop our content service-and knowledge appropriate for them. add that some of the companies that advertise in our [Sathacks](http://www.sathacks.net/) may look to use cookies and web special to us and you, and these companies, for example, [Google](http://www.google.com/) and the [Google AdSense advertising program](https://www.google.com/adsense/login/en_US/?hl=en_US&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-en_US-et-ads&medium=link&gsessionid=rZcHLpemZWE) is the first advertising company in our site.And, of course, declared Such companies, which are the third party in the privacy policy is pursuing such data and ad networks for the purpose of improving the quality of their ads and measure their effectiveness. As this happens and under agreements with us entitled to use technical means (such as cookies, network settings, and BB special software JavaScript) for the same purposes mentioned above and which are summarized in the development of advertising content for these companies measure the effectiveness of these ads, without any other goals may hurt in one way or another on our visitors.Of course, the [Sathacks](http://www.sathacks.net/) no access to or control over these cookies, and even after you approve you for taking them out of your device (cookies), and also consider ourselves are not responsible in any way for the illegal use her that happened, God forbid.You review the privacy policy of the third party in this document ([advertisers Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/login/en_US/?hl=en_US&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-en_US-et-ads&medium=link&gsessionid=rZcHLpemZWE)) servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and its various activities.To review the privacy policy of the first advertising program in [Sathacks](http://www.sathacks.net/) [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/login/en_US/?hl=en_US&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-en_US-et-ads&medium=link&gsessionid=rZcHLpemZWE) and a subsidiary of [Google](http://www.google.com/), please [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)Finally .. We are obligated under the terms of this Agreement that show you how to disable cookies, where you can do so through your individual browser options, [or by privacy Mtabahsaash the Google ad and content network.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)If you need any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, do not hesitate to contact us by e-mail at: here[Sathacks Team](http://www.sathacks.net/)  
The terms of this policy can be developed and the change in its content at any time we deem necessary**
